quizData = [
	{
		"question":"Lean in: Women, work and the will to lead” is a book written by?",
		"questionOpt1":"Sandra Lerner",
		"questionOpt2":"Sheryl Sandberg",
		"questionOpt3":"Marrisa Mayor",
		"questionOpt4":"Meg Whitman",
		"rightAnswer":"Sheryl Sandberg",
	},
	{
		"question":"She was an analyst of Charles Babbage’s analytical engine and is considered by many the “first computer programmer. Who’s she?",
		"questionOpt1":"Ada Lovelace",
		"questionOpt2":"Grace Hopper",
		"questionOpt3":"Ursula Burns",
		"questionOpt4":"Sophie Wilson",
		"rightAnswer":"Ada Lovelace",
	},
	{
		"question":"Which woman developed the algorithm behind the spanning tree protocol?",
		"questionOpt1":"Radia Perlman",
		"questionOpt2":"Tarah wheeler",
		"questionOpt3":"Marrisa Mayor",
		"questionOpt4":"Jean E. Sammet",
		"rightAnswer":"Radia Perlman",
	},
	{
		"question":"Ada Lovelace is celebrated as being the world’s first ever computer programmer. Which of these facts is not true about her?",
		"questionOpt1":"She is the daughter of poet Lord Byron",
		"questionOpt2":"She conceptualised a flying machine aged 12",
		"questionOpt3":"She was partially blind",
		"questionOpt4":"Her mentor was mathematician (and inventor of what would have been the world’s first computer) Charles Babbage
",
		"rightAnswer":"She was partially blind",
	},
	{
		"question":"Which of these tech giants does NOT currently have a female CEO?",
		"questionOpt1":"YouTube",
		"questionOpt2":"IBM",
		"questionOpt3":"HPE",
		"questionOpt4":"Trend Micro",
		"rightAnswer":"HPE",
	},
	{
		"question":"Of the 35 large resellers whose pay gap reports CRN examined, which had the lowest median pay gap, at 7.3 per cent?",
		"questionOpt1":"Softcat",
		"questionOpt2":"Daisy",
		"questionOpt3":"RM",
		"questionOpt4":"Computacenter",
		"rightAnswer":"RM",
	},
	{
		"question":"The median pay gap among UK firms in general stands at 9.7 per cent, according to the BBC. CRN conducted similar analysis of the pay gap reports of the 35 largest UK resellers. What was their average median pay gap?",
		"questionOpt1":"3%",
		"questionOpt2":"23%",
		"questionOpt3":"33%",
		"questionOpt4":"13%",
		"rightAnswer":"23%",
	},
	{
		"question":"Meg Whitman exited her job as CEO of HPE in January to join start-up NewTV. But which tech start-up did she take from $4m to $8bn revenues during her stint there between 1998 and 2008?",
		"questionOpt1":"Google",
		"questionOpt2":"Amazon",
		"questionOpt3":"Juniper Networks",
		"questionOpt4":"eBay",
		"rightAnswer":"eBay",
	},
	{
		"question":"Computer science pioneer Mary Kenneth Keller (who helped develop the basic programming language which would be brought to the masses via the ZX Spectrum in the 1980s) was also a:",
		"questionOpt1":"Nun",
		"questionOpt2":"Botanist",
		"questionOpt3":"Pianist",
		"questionOpt4":"Prominent Quaker",
		"rightAnswer":"Nun",
	},
	{
		"question":"How many of the world’s 206 technology billionaires are women, according to Forbes’ Rich List 2018?",
		"questionOpt1":"2",
		"questionOpt2":"5",
		"questionOpt3":"10",
		"questionOpt4":"15",
		"rightAnswer":"15",
	},
	{
		"question":"Which of these global reseller giants has a female CEO?",
		"questionOpt1":"SHI",
		"questionOpt2":"CDW",
		"questionOpt3":"Insight",
		"questionOpt4":"World Wide Technologies",
		"rightAnswer":"SHI",
	},
	{
		"question":"According to the Chartered Institute for IT, the percentage of UK IT workers that are female is:",
		"questionOpt1":"10",
		"questionOpt2":"17",
		"questionOpt3":"24",
		"questionOpt4":"31",
		"rightAnswer":"17",
	},
	{
		"question":"At 8.4%, which of these vendor giants reported the lowest (median) gender pay gap for its UK business in the run up to the 4 April reporting deadline?",
		"questionOpt1":"Microsoft",
		"questionOpt2":"Dell",
		"questionOpt3":"Oracle",
		"questionOpt4":"Cisco",
		"rightAnswer":"Microsoft",
	},
	{
		"question":"Lovelace’s ideas about computing were far ahead of her time. Roughly how long was it before the age of computer science dawned and technology is generally acknowledged to have caught up?",
		"questionOpt1":"20",
		"questionOpt2":"50",
		"questionOpt3":"100",
		"questionOpt4":"150",
		"rightAnswer":"100",
	},
	{
		"question":"Who is the world’s richest female tech tycoon, according to Forbes’ Rich List 2018?",
		"questionOpt1":"Denis Coates (founder of bet365)",
		"questionOpt2":"Zhou Qunfei (chairman of Lens Technology)",
		"questionOpt3":"Meg Whitman (NewTV)",
		"questionOpt4":"Eva Chen (CEO of Trend Micro)",
		"rightAnswer":"Zhou Qunfei (chairman of Lens Technology)",
	},
	{
		"question":"Which of these women led the team that created the first computer language compiler, which led to the popular COBOL language",
		"questionOpt1":"Grace Hopper",
		"questionOpt2":"Ada Lovelace",
		"questionOpt3":"Dorothy Hodgkin",
		"questionOpt4":"Adele Goldberg",
		"rightAnswer":"Grace Hopper",
	},
	


	{	
		"question":"Mathematician Ada Lovelace wrote the first computer program. Which of the following is not true about her?",
		"questionOpt1":"She was Lord Byron’s only legitimate child",
		"questionOpt2":"Her program ran successfully on Babbage’s Analytical Engine",
		"questionOpt3":"The United States Department of Defense named a programming language in her honour",
		"questionOpt4":"She accumulated huge gambling debts using a failed betting system",
		"rightAnswer":"Her program ran successfully on Babbages Analytical Engine",
	},
	{	
		"question":"Marissa Mayer is CEO of Yahoo. Where was she before?",
		"questionOpt1":"Apple",
		"questionOpt2":"Facebook",
		"questionOpt3":"Googler",
		"questionOpt4":"IBM",
		"rightAnswer":"Google",
	},

	{	
		"question":"Which programming language did Admiral Grace Hopper co-create in 1959?",
		"questionOpt1":"BASIC",
		"questionOpt2":"FORTRAN",
		"questionOpt3":"C",
		"questionOpt4":"COBOL",
		"rightAnswer":"COBOL",
	},

	{	
		"question":"British developer Clare Sutcliffe has set up an initiative to get kids programming in school. What is it called?",
		"questionOpt1":"Code Clubs",
		"questionOpt2":"Make Things Do Stuff",
		"questionOpt3":"The National Curriculum (ICT section)",
		"questionOpt4":"Code Champs",
		"rightAnswer":"Code Clubs",
	},

	{	
		"question":"Joanna Shields was appointed what by the UK government?",
		"questionOpt1":"Under-Secretary of State Minister for e-commerce",
		"questionOpt2":"Under-Secretary of State Minister for Internet Safety & Security",
		"questionOpt3":"Under-Secretary of State Minister for ICT education",
		"questionOpt4":"None of the above",
		"rightAnswer":"Under-Secretary of State Minister for Internet Safety & Security",
	},

	{	
		"question":"Dame Stephanie Shirley founded software firm FI in 1962. What was special about it?",
		"questionOpt1":"It outsourced work from India",
		"questionOpt2":"It pioneered educational software",
		"questionOpt3":"It employed 99 percent women",
		"questionOpt4":"All of the above",
		"rightAnswer":"It employed 99 percent women",
	},

	{	
		"question":"What percentage, roughly, of tech CEOs are women?",
		"questionOpt1":"4 percent",
		"questionOpt2":"10 percent",
		"questionOpt3":"20 percent",
		"questionOpt4":"30 percent",
		"rightAnswer":"4 percent",
	},



	{	
		"question":"What company did Diane Greene found in 1998?",
		"questionOpt1":"Yahoo",
		"questionOpt2":"Salesforce",
		"questionOpt3":"VMware",
		"questionOpt4":"Cisco",
		"rightAnswer":"VMware",
	},

	{	
		"question":"Which company has Meg Whitman NOT been CEO of?",
		"questionOpt1":"HP",
		"questionOpt2":"Hasbro",
		"questionOpt3":"eBay",
		"questionOpt4":"Yahoo",
		"rightAnswer":"Hasbro",
	},

	{	
		"question":"According to former EU Commissioner for the Digital Agenda Neelie Kroes, what proportion of ICT workers are women?",
		"questionOpt1":"10 percent",
		"questionOpt2":"30 percent",
		"questionOpt3":"40 percent",
		"questionOpt4":"50 percent",
		"rightAnswer":"30 percent",
	},

{	
	"question":"Which hosting company does Kate Craig-Wood head up?",
	"questionOpt1":"Memset",
	"questionOpt2":"UKfast",
	"questionOpt3":"GoDaddy",
	"questionOpt4":"Wix",
	"rightAnswer":"Memset",
		},

{	
	"question":" Which open source group does Mitchell Baker lead?",
	"questionOpt1":"Libre Office",
	"questionOpt2":"Apache",
	"questionOpt3":"CNCF",
	"questionOpt4":"Mozilla Foundation",
	"rightAnswer":"Mozilla Foundation",
		},

{	
	"question":"Not just an exception: All these companies have had a female CEO more than once... except which one?",
	"questionOpt1":"Xerox",
	"questionOpt2":"HP",
	"questionOpt3":"eBay",
	"questionOpt4":"Yahoo!",
	"rightAnswer":"eBay",
		},

{	
	"question":"Padmasree Warrior was the CTO for which tech giant?",
	"questionOpt1":"Juniper",
	"questionOpt2":"Cisco",
	"questionOpt3":"EMC",
	"questionOpt4":"VMware",
	"rightAnswer":"Cisco",
		},

{	
	"question":"Sheryl Sandberg is COO of Facebook. What is her book called?",
	"questionOpt1":"The Women's Room",
	"questionOpt2":"Lean In",
	"questionOpt3":"Dismantle Patriarchy",
	"questionOpt4":"Women who code",
	"rightAnswer":"Lean In",
},

{	
	"question":"A survey in November 2016 found female tech employees were on average paid less than men by which percentage?",
	"questionOpt1":"10 percent",
	"questionOpt2":"20 percent",
	"questionOpt3":"30 percent",
	"questionOpt4":"40 percent",
	"rightAnswer":"20 percent",
		},

{	
	"question":"Who’s the current CEO of YouTube and also called the “most important person in advertising”?",
	"questionOpt1":"Susan wojcicki",
	"questionOpt2":"Augustus Ada Byron",
	"questionOpt3":"Tarah wheeler",
	"questionOpt4":"Sandra Lerner",
	"rightAnswer":"Susan wojcicki",
		},


{	
	"question":"Who’s the first woman to head IBM?",
	"questionOpt1":"Susan Kare",
	"questionOpt2":"Susan wojcicki",
	"questionOpt3":"Meg Whitman",
	"questionOpt4":"Virginia Rometty",
	"rightAnswer":"Virginia Rometty",
		},

{	
	"question":"Mostly Recognized for her contribution to Ethernet technology,Who’s referred to as the “Mother of Internet”?",
	"questionOpt1":"Susan Kare",
	"questionOpt2":"Radia perlman",
	"questionOpt3":"Joan Ball",
	"questionOpt4":"Virginia Rometty",
	"rightAnswer":"Radia perlman",
		},

{	
	"question":"Who’s the first black woman to head a fortune 500 company, Xerox Corporation?",
	"questionOpt1":"Ursula Burns",
	"questionOpt2":"Dorothy Vaughan",
	"questionOpt3":"Mary Jackson",
	"questionOpt4":"Joan Ball",
	"rightAnswer":"Ursula Burns",
		},

{	
	"question":"Who was the first person to start a computer dating service in 1964?",
	"questionOpt1":"Jean E. Sammet",
	"questionOpt2":"Susan Kare",
	"questionOpt3":"Joan Ball",
	"questionOpt4":"Sophie Wilson",
	"rightAnswer":"Joan Ball",
		},

{	
	"question":"Who is best known for creation of the Google Android logo including its green robot icon.?",
	"questionOpt1":"Mary Lou Jepsen",
	"questionOpt2":"Irina Blok",
	"questionOpt3":"Melanie Rieback",
	"questionOpt4":"None of the above",
	"rightAnswer":"Irina Blok",
		},

{	
	"question":"Who’s work with spread spectrum technology led to the development of GPS, Bluetooth, and Wi-Fi?",
	"questionOpt1":"Hedy Lamarr",
	"questionOpt2":"Sarah Friar",
	"questionOpt3":"Ellen Pao",
	"questionOpt4":"Kathryn Minshew",
	"rightAnswer":"Hedy Lamarr",
		},

{	
	"question":"”Innovating Women: The Changing Face of Technology” is written by?",
	"questionOpt1":"Vikrant Khanna",
	"questionOpt2":"Shikha Mathur Kumar",
	"questionOpt3":"None of the Above",
	"questionOpt4":"Vivek Wadhwa, Farai Chideya",
	"rightAnswer":"Vivek Wadhwa, Farai Chideya",
},

{	
	"question":"Who is best known for being the female American voice of Apple’s “Siri” since the service was introduced on the iPhone 4S?",
	"questionOpt1":"Jen Taylor",
	"questionOpt2":"20 percent",
	"questionOpt3":"Susan Bennett",
	"questionOpt4":"40 percent",
	"rightAnswer":"20 percent",
},



]

